Guide to the Aaron Cometbus Punk and Underground Press Collection, ca. 1977-2013.
Cometbus, Aaron Punk and Underground Press Collection
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Aaron Cometbus Punk and Underground Press Collection, ca. 1977-2013.
8107
Cometbus, Aaron,
14.9 cubic feet
Flyers, printed material, posters, photographs, correspondence, and ephemera.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Flyers, posters, magazines, files, and zines relating to American punk and alternative culture collected or created by Aaron Cometbus, including his own work as a writer and musician.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Aaron Elliott, better known as Aaron Cometbus, has published Cometbus magazine since 1981. He is also an accomplished novelist, lyricist, and drummer.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Flyers, posters, magazines, files, and zines relating to American punk and alternative culture collected or created by Aaron Cometbus, including his own work as a writer and musician. The archive contains hundreds of fanzines and small magazines, plus original manuscripts and paste-ups for Cometbus and related publishing and distribution records. Board games, business cards, set lists, and venue histories provide a personal, behind-the-scenes view of punk both as music and as a movement, from 1980 to the present.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cometbus, Aaron, 1968-
Subjects:
Underground press publications -- California -- Berkeley.; Underground press publications -- United States.; Protest movements -- California -- Berkeley; Counterculture -- California -- Berkeley; Counterculture -- California; Underground press publications -- California; Underground press -- California; Punk culture.; Punk Culture -- United States.; Punk rock music.; Punk rock music; Punk rock music; Punk rock music; Punk rock musicians.
Places:
Berkeley (Calif.); Alameda County (Calif.)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
NOTES
Introduction to the collection written by Aaron Elliot can be found in Box 1, Folder A.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Punk and Underground Press Materials
a. Bay Area
1. Titles A-O
2. Titles P-Z
b. Other Locations
1. Titles A-D
2. Titles E-O
3. Titles P-Z
c. Underground Newspapers
1. 1960s Underground Newspapers
2. High School Underground Newspapers
d. Other Zine Material
e. Cometbus & Related Materials
1. Cometbus Issues
2. Cometbus Drafts and Proofs
3. Cometbus Files
Series II. Event Flyers and Posters
a. Flyers
1. Assorted
2. Shows: Bay Area
3. Shows: Other Locations
4. Other Types of Flyers
b. Posters
Series III. Political Materials
Series IV. Venue Materials
Series V. Band Files & Related Materials
Series VI. Ephemera
a. Photographs
b. Assorted Ephemera
c. Board Games
Series VII. Sound Recordings
Series VIII. Letters to Cometbus Magazine
CONTAINER LIST
- Introductory essay, 2016 (Box 1, Folder a)
- "Anarchy in the Archives" edition of Cometbus, 2016 (Box 1, Folder a)
- Series I. Punk and Underground Press Materials, 1963-2016
  Includes fanzines, magazines, newsletters, comics, and newspapers
  The first two subseries are arranged geographically starting with locations in the Bay Area and then alphabetically by title within each location.
  - Bay Area, 1977-2010
    - Titles A-O, 1980-2016
      - 22, 1994-1996; Daria (Box 1, Folder 1)
        No. 2-3
        San Francisco, California
      - 49 Square Miles of Surprises, Undated; SF Bike Messenger Association; Church of Rotating Mass (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Absolutely Zippo, 1988-06-1996; Eggplant, Robert (Box 1, Folder 2)
        No. 2-3, 6, 8-12, 15-17, 25, 30
        Pinole, California; Berkeley, California
      - Absolutely Zippo, 1989-2005; Eggplant, Robert (Box 12, Folder 2)
        No. 11, 21, 23
        Pinole, California
        Berkeley, California
      - Aim Your Dick, 1992; Nguyen, Mimi; Marike (Box 1, Folder 3)
        No. 1
      - Another Opening, 1984-07-12-1984-07-19; Caroline (Box 1, Folder 4)
        Walnut Creek, California
      - Another Room, 1980-1985; Childs, Lucy; Gullak, John (Box 7, Folder 2)
        No. 2, 5, 7-8, Vol. 2 No. 5, 7, 10, Vol. 3 No. 1-2, 5, 6, 8
        Oakland, California
      - Another Room, 1980-1985; Childs, Lucy; Gullak, John (Box 9, Folder 11)
        Vol. 1, No. 2, 10
      - Angels We Have Heard While High, Undated; Sinister, Bucky (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Antiseptic, 1981-1982-02; Mitchen, Kate; Big DaDa Art Enterprises (Box 1, Folder 5)
        No. 1 (2 copies), 2-3, 4 (2 copies)
        Berkeley, California; Oakland, California
      - Appeal to Reason, 1982-1984; Bryan, John (Box 8, Folder 1)
        Vol. 1 No. 4-5, 16
      - Bad Thoughts, 1999; Padilla, Amanda (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Benzene, 1991; Sally, Zak (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Berkeley Madness, 1984; Nuhrodik, Nick; Nuhrodik, Nell (Box 1, Folder 7)
        No. 2
      - Berkeley Sucks, 1989-1990; Townley, Jesse (Box 1, Folder 8)
        No. 1, 3
      - Between the Lines, 1986-04-03-1986-04-15 (Box 1, Folder 9)
        Vol. 1, No. 3, Vol. 2 No. 2 (2 copies), 3-4
      - Beware, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
        No. 3
      - Biko Plaza News, 1985-05-01-1985-10-18 (Box 1, Folder 11)
        Vol. 1 No. 1 (2 copies), 4 (2 copies), 5, 7, 11, 14-15, 18 (3 copies), 19, 20 (2 copies), 21, 22 (2 copies), 25, 27 (2 copies), 29, 33-35; Vol. 2 No. 23; Vol. 3 No. 1, 3 (2 copies), 4, 5 (2 copies), 6, 8
      - Biko Plaza News, 1985-06-27 (Box 7, Folder 5)
        Vol. 2 No. 5
      - Blackmail and Other Good Intentions, 1998-07-1998-11; Grove, Erika; Hynes, Patrick (Box 1, Folder 12)
        No. 1-2
      - Boy, Does High School Ever Suck, 1991-11; Meline, Gabe (Box 12, Folder 6)
        No. 6
        Santa Rosa, California
      - Breakfast Without Meat, 1983-1990; Gray, Lizzy Kate; Turkington, Gregg (Box 1, Folder 13)
        No. 3-8, 9 (2 copies), 10, 13
      - Broccoli Makes Me Sad!, 1988; Dodge, Chris (Box 12, Folder 7)
        San Jose, California
      - Cafe, 1991-04; Brooks, Martin (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Can of Worms, 1990-04; Sylene, N.; Rhoys, S.B. (Box 1, Folder 14)
        Colma, California
      - Carrion Crow, 2003-01-2003-02; Hatton, Dave (Box 1, Folder 15)
        Pleasant Hill, California
      - Catbox Room, The, 1995; Maslowe, Lisa (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Cheetah, Oh Sweet Cheetah, 1991-1993; Ducky; Van (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Chiroptera, 1996; Rachel (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Christ on a Crutch, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Cigarette Philosophy, 1980-1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Circular, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
        No. 4
      - Coffee No Girl, 1995-04-1996; Carolyn (Box 1, Folder 19)
        No. 2 (2 copies), 3
        Olympia, Washington; Oakland, California
      - Cool Beans!, 1992-1994; Kelly, Matt (Box 1, Folder 20)
        Berkeley, California; San Francisco, California
      - Creep, 1981; Creep, Mickey; Creep, Danny (Box 1, Folder 6)
        Vol. 1 No. 1
        Includes half issue of Basement
      - Daily Battle, The, 1984-05 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Daily Californian, The, 1986-01-24; Anderson, Craig (Box 7, Folder 8)
        Vol. XVIII No. 3
      - Daily Lobe, 1984-10-21 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Dangerous Times, The, 1990; Josh (Box 12, Folder 11)
        No. 18
      - Deadbeat, 1987-09; Deadbeat, Frank; Lubinski, Richard (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Devil in the Dishes, The, 1994-01-1994-07; Davey (Box 1, Folder 23)
        Berkeley, California; Bristol, Connecticut
      - Diseaster Now for Future Love, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 9)
        Vol. 1 No. 3
      - Dishwasher, 1990; Pete (Box 1, Folder 24)
        No. 5
      - Dogs in Heat, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - Doris, 1996-09-2006; Crabb, Cindy (Box 3, Folder 4)
        No. 6-7, 12, 18, 20,32
        Asheville, North Carolina; Berkeley, California
      - Duh!, 1982; Donohue, Bill (Box 1, Folder 26)
        Vol. 1 No. 2
      - Earth First!, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 11)
        Canyon, California
      - East Bay Undergrounder, 1985-08-03; Thomas, Craig (Box 12, Folder 12)
        Piedmont, California
      - Eat It Up, 1981-10-1981-11; Void, Frank (Box 1, Folder 27)
        No. 7-9
        New York, New York; Berkeley, California
      - Echo Line, 1985; Antolin, Emmanuelle (Box 1, Folder 28)
      - Ego, 1982-08; Belsito, Peter (Box 1, Folder 29)
      - Epi-Logue - The Zine of Epicenter Zone's Demise, 1995; Zola, Gordon (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Filth, 1996-06; Collison, Rob; Donohoe, Joe; Sperry, Chuck; Wylie, Daniel (Box 7, Folder 13)
        No. 22
      - Five O'Clock Charlie, 1989-06-1989-11; Duncan, Douglas; Loftus, Kyle; Honeycutt, Erik D. (Box 1, Folder 30)
        Vol. 1 No. 1 (2 copies)
      - Forget It!, 1982-03-1982-05; Howard Etc. (Box 1, Folder 31)
        No. 7
      - Get Off My Wagon, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - Goblins Army, 1997; Sean (Box 12, Folder 14)
        No. 2.4
      - Gone!, 1985-08-1986-04; Tucson, Denver (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Gorath, 1984; Evans, Barrie (Box 1, Folder 34)
      - Gozar My Love, 1992; Zedo (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - Grassroots, 1980-08-13-1982-07-13 (Box 9, Folder 23)
        Vol. 9, No. 3, Vol. 10, No. 24
      - H.R., 2001; Casselman, Kristen (Box 1, Folder 35)
      - Haight Ashbury Free Press, 1994-04; Hoffman, David (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Heuristic Squelch, The, 1994-05; Greenberg, Josh; Hertzer, Keith; Seifert, Mark (Box 7, Folder 15)
        Vol. 4 No. 6
      - Hex, 1993-09-1995-02; Jane (Box 1, Folder 37)
        No. 1-3
        Olympia, Washington; Berkeley, California
      - Hog Callings, 1990-09-1990-12; Cedar (Box 7, Folder 16)
        Vol. 1 No. 6
      - Hot Lava Monster, 1992-05-1993-07; Bitz (Jennifer) (Box 1, Folder 38)
        No. 1-2, 4
        San Diego, California; Daly City, California
      - Hysteria Action Forum, 1993-03-1993-05 (Box 1, Folder 39)
      - I Gotta Get This Off My Chest, Undated; A Book a Week Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - Incoherent House, 1985-1986; Waltz, Mitzi (Box 1, Folder 40)
        No. 1, 3, 5, 7
      - In the Corner, 1993-08; Angela (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - Inkling, Undated; Klein, Melissa (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - Jank, 1995-03-1998-02; Janelle; Jeff (Box 1, Folder 41)
        No. 1, 6 (2copies), 7-10
      - Javaman, 1991; Lutzenberger, Tom (Box 1, Folder 42)
        Moraga, California
      - Jettlag, 1981; King, Jilliannette; Jacuzzi Concept Enterprises, NoCo. (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Junk Magnet, 1996-1999; Freeman, Nicholas (Box 1, Folder 43)
        Vol. 1 No. 5, 7
      - Ker-bloom!, 2006-03-2006-06; Artnoose (Box 1, Folder 44)
        No. 59-60
      - Last Days, 1987; Normal, Davy (Box 1, Folder 45)
        Kentfield, California
      - Laughed Like Hyenas, 1984; Nancy (Box 1, Folder 46)
      - Laundramat Mecca, 1994-05-1994-06 (Box 1, Folder 47)
      - Lillian, 1992; Grace (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - Live Wild or Die, 1989-1994; Daniel (Box 7, Folder 19)
        No. 2-3, 5
      - Lobotomized Visions, 1984; Borruso, John (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - Make Up that Clogs Pores, 1982; Grux (Box 1, Folder 48)
      - Matter of Image, A, 1985; Yee, Eric (Box 1, Folder 49)
        San Leandro, California
      - Maximum Rocknroll, 1983-03-1984-02 (Box 1, Folder 50)
        No. 5-8, 11
      - Maximum Rocknroll, 1984-03-1989-12 (Box 1, Folder 51)
        No. 12, 17-18, 49, 79
      - Maximum Rocknroll, 1992-01-1993-03 (Box 1, Folder 52)
        No. 104, 110, 118
      - Maximum Rocknroll, 1993-12-2009-04 (Box 1, Folder 53)
        No. 127, 311
      - Maximum Rocknroll, 2003-10-2010-02 (Box 12, Folder 21)
        No. 245, 291, 321
      - Maybe, 1993-1994; Cohen, Shosh (Box 1, Folder 54)
        No. 5, 7
      - Monthly Independent Tribune Times Journal Post Gazette News Chronicle Bulletin, The, 1983-03-1996-08; Child, T.S. (Box 1, Folder 55)
        No. 3 (2 copies), 6, 7 (2 copies), 9-12, 16, 18, 21-22, 24, 25 (2 copies), 26-29, 31, 33-35, 37-38, 39 (2 copies), 42-43, 46, 49, 51-53, 56-57, 60-61, 63, 65, 67
      - Mother, Undated; Mullery, Sue; Dee, Denise; Schneck, Carol; Hilary (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - Muckraker, The, 1997; McMahon, David (Box 12, Folder 23)
      - Mudflap, 1992; Snider, Greta (Box 12, Folder 24)
      - Murder Can Be Fun, 1987-2004; Marr, John (Box 1, Folder 56)
        No. 19
      - Murder Can Be Fun Presents: Obscure Crime Books, 1994; Marr, John (Box 1, Folder 57)
      - Muse, 1997; Madonna, Paul (Box 12, Folder 25)
        No. 10
      - Music Calendar, 1984-01-1984-02; Fauna, Flora (Box 7, Folder 20)
        Vol. 3 No. 2-3
      - My Letter to the World, 1993-01-1993-12; Lily (Box 1, Folder 58)
        Vol. 1 No. 1-4, 8
      - Nart, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 59)
      - Naughty Nomads, 1989; Dettman, John (Box 12, Folder 26)
      - Neapolitan Mews, The, The Social Club (Box 12, Folder 27)
      - Nipple Ring Tittie Twist, 1995-01-1997-07; Krider, Rob (Box 1, Folder 60)
        No. 1, 7
        Napa, California
      - No Porridge For Oliver (N.P.F.O.), 2003-2005; Lane, Cedro (Box 1, Folder 61)
      - Non, 1986-1993 (Box 1, Folder 62)
      - Not, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 63)
      - Notes from the Dead Letter Office, Undated; De Julius (Box 12, Folder 28)
        Vallejo, California
      - Notes from the Lighthouse, 1991; Baker, Josh (Box 1, Folder 64)
        No. 1 (2 copies), 2
      - Odis, 1985-06; Vandrick, Paul; Claw (Box 12, Folder 29)
      - Ology, 1989-09-1995; Montgomery, Peter (Box 1, Folder 65)
        Vol. 1 No. 1-3
      - One Story, Undated; Julie (Box 12, Folder 30)
      - Open City, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 4)
        No. 255-256
      - Out, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 66)
        Hayward, California
      - Out of Order, Lewis, Peter (Box 1, Folder 67)
        No. 5, 7, 9
        Occidental, California
      - Outpunk, 1995-06; Wobensmith, Matt (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Titles P-Z, 1977-2010
      - Paintspot, 1994-03-28; Chris (Box 1, Folder 69)
      - Paralyzed, 1993-04; Coolman, Alex (Box 12, Folder 32)
      - People Under No King (PUNK), 1993-03-2000-08; Seger, Rick; Seger, Susan (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Perv, 1981; Ghia, Carmen (Creep, Danny) (Box 1, Folder 70)
      - Pigeon, 2002-11; Juliette (Box 1, Folder 71)
      - Poke-a-dot, 1981; Quazar, Marzy (Box 1, Folder 72)
        Donor note: the 1st Berkeley punk zine
      - Poland 1982, 1982-01-10 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Positively 4th Street, Undated; Meline, Gabe (Box 12, Folder 33)
      - Postazine, 1984; Cain, Sarah; Mozer, Dana; Lieben Und Arbeitan (Box 2, Folder 84)
      - Promise, The, 1992; Kennedy, Jeffery (Box 12, Folder 34)
      - Protest and Survive, 1984-07; Treggiari, Jo (Box 2, Folder 2)
        Emeryville, California
      - P.O.R.T. (Provocateur of Random Thought), 1984-06-1985; K., Sallee (Box 12, Folder 31)
        Vol. 1, No. 2-3 and Vol.2, No. 5-6
        Palo Alto, California
        Boston, Massachusetts
      - Psycho Transcriber, 1995-02-1995-07; Grace; Lillian (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Psycho-babble, 1990-1999; Fitzgerald, Ty (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Puddle, 1991; Applecore, Chris (Box 12, Folder 35)
      - Puncture, 1983-06-1983-08; Spielmann, Katherine (Box 2, Folder 5)
        Vol. 1 No. 4
      - Punk Calendar, 1993; Meline, Gabe (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Puppydoglove, 1994-12; Arsenault, Marc (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Rake, 1990; Buono, Brian (Box 12, Folder 36)
      - Riders on the BART, 1991; Zenick, Jeff (Box 12, Folder 37)
      - Rip It Up, 1998-06-1999-02 (Box 2, Folder 8)
        No. 4-5
      - Ripper, 1983-01-13; Tonooka, Tim (Box 2, Folder 9)
        No. 8
      - Round Robin Rides, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 38)
      - Rutabaga, 1991; Räzl; Bitz (Box 2, Folder 10)
        No. 1, 2 (2 copies)
      - Saboteur, 1984-10-1985-08; Hepting, Rick (Box 9, Folder 1)
        Vol. 1 No. 1, Vol. 2 No. 1
      - Samantha Jane Dorsett Tribute Zine, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 39)
      - Schralp, 1986-05 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Search & Destroy, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Sister Spit, 1994; Anderson, Sini; Tea, Michelle (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Skeleton Quarterly, The, 1986-01-1990-05; Lollar, Phil (Box 2, Folder 13)
        No. 1-4, 9-11
      - Sleeping Dogs, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Slingshot, 1988-04-18-1991-01-30 (Box 2, Folder 15)
        Vol. 1 No. 8, 12, 28, 41
      - Slingshot, 1989-09-2010-05 (Box 9, Folder 3)
        Vol. 1 No. 30, 42-43, 62, 96, 99-100, 102, 104.1
      - Sparrow, Undated; Cowgill, Skott (Box 12, Folder 40)
      - Spunk, 2000-06-2000-08; Jones, Violet (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Standard Deviation, 1991-08; Lindsey (Box 12, Folder 41)
        Arcata, California
      - Step Off, 1994; Fortner, Eric (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Storms of Youth, 1982-04 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Story of It, The, 1984; Aki, Zenta (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Subdued Violence, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 42)
      - Tales of Blarg, 1996; Hessig, Janelle (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Tall Tales, Undated; Casual T. (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Tedium, 1982-1983; Michaels, Jesse (Box 2, Folder 22)
        Kensington, California
      - Telegraph Underground, 1991-03; Brooks, Martin (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - This is East Bay, Not L.A.!, 2008-07 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Too Far, 1986-1990; Droogas, Adrienne (Box 2, Folder 24)
        No. 4, 8, 10
        Oakland, California; San Francisco, California
      - Trashola, 1982-1983; Morton, Jim (Box 2, Folder 25)
        Vol. 2 No. 1-2, 12, 16, Vol. 3 No. 7
      - Trashola, 1982; Morton, Jim (Box 2, Folder 85)
        Vol. 1, No. 12 (2 copies), 15, Vol. 3, No. 3, 7
      - Treasure Trove, 1996-06-1999-09; Sollberger, Eva M. (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Twisted Image, 1982; Backwords, Ace; Duncan, Bruce (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Unmentionable, The, 1990-03-1991-07; Kelina (Box 2, Folder 27)
        No. 11-13
        Berkeley, California; Santa Cruz, California
      - Unsound, 1983; Davenport, William; Rankin, Christopher (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Urban Guerrilla, 1997-2000; Unidos, Jay (Box 2, Folder 29)
        No. 1, 4-5
      - Vegetarian Skaters for Social Responsibility, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 43)
      - Vertical Urge, 1985-11-1986; Loobkoff, Sergie (Box 2, Folder 30)
        Vol. 1 No. 1-3, 6
      - Wajlemac, 1987-1989; Morf, Devon (Box 2, Folder 31)
        No. 4, 6, 8
        Larkspur, California
      - Waterworks, Undated; Brewster, Elise; Cowen, Stuart; Grossinger, Robin; Langstaff, Katy (Box 17, Folder 10)
        Art related zine about reclaimed shopping carts.
      - Wave Sector, 1981-06-1982-02; Farragher, Marcella (Box 9, Folder 13)
        Vol. 1 No. 1, 7
      - Why Music Sucks, 1995-06-1996-02; Kogan, Frank (Box 2, Folder 32)
        No. 8-9
      - Why Music Sucks, 1995-06-1998-03; Kogan, Frank (Box 2, Folder 33)
        No. 10, 12
      - Why Music Sucks, 1997-06; Kogan, Frank (Box 12, Folder 44)
        No. 11
      - Wordburger, 1990-1991-05; Burgie, Ed (Box 2, Folder 34)
        No. 9-10, 15-16
      - Xerox Mouth, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 35)
        No. 9 (2 copies), 20
      - You Could See the Sea, 2001-08; Klein, Melissa (Box 1, Folder 36)
      - You Suck, 1991; Rocky (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Other Locations, 1978-2015
    - Titles A-D, 1980-2015
      - 1 Size Fits All, Undated; Kristen (Box 12, Folder 45)
        Houston, Texas
      - 2% Homogenized, 1996-1997; Phil (Box 2, Folder 37)
        No. 3-4
        Madison, Wisconsin; Fremont, Ohio
      - 2nz, 1982; Longo, Thomas; Bland, Richard S. (Box 2, Folder 38)
        Minneapolis, Minnesota
      - Alphabet Threat, 1990-1999 (Box 7, Folder 1)
        No. 2-3, 7
        Sacramento, California
      - American Dream, The - Minifications, 1994-06; McGuff, Luke (Box 2, Folder 39)
        No. 14
        Seattle, Washington
      - American Job, 1987-12-1994-11; Russell, Randy; Toboso Publications (Box 2, Folder 40)
        Sandusky, Ohio; Portland, Oregon
      - Amigo, 1988; Worker, Jay (Box 2, Folder 41)
        Chula Vista, California
      - Andy's Chair, 1992-1994-09; Arsenault, Marc (Box 2, Folder 42)
        Schenectady, New York
      - Angry Thoreauan, 1992-01-1992-02; Tin-Ear, Randy (Box 12, Folder 46)
        Anaheim, California
      - Annu Vrre, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 47)
        Tumba, Sweden
      - Another Pair of Shoes, 1993-04-19; J (Box 2, Folder 43)
        No. 12
      - Anti-Social Jr., 1984; Roberts, Ken (Box 12, Folder 48)
        Chicago, Illinois
      - APM, 1984-02-1984-03; Group Six (Box 7, Folder 3)
        Unknown Location
      - A-Political, 1986-04-25; Seger, Rick (Box 2, Folder 44)
        Atascadero, California
      - Arnie, 1994-02-1997; B., Alex; Gane, Simon; Pars; T., Mark (Box 2, Folder 45)
        No. 2, 6
        Wiltshire, United Kingdom
      - Artichoke Tales, 2001-2002; Kelso, Megan (Box 2, Folder 46)
        Seattle, Washington; Brooklyn, New York
      - Assassin and the Whiner, The, 1995-1997; McNinch, Carrie; Stastny, Ed (Box 12, Folder 49)
        No. 4, 7
        Los Angeles, California
      - Atakra, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - August Spies Zine, 1997-01-16; Brian (Box 12, Folder 50)
        Sioux Falls, South Dakota
      - Auto Pilot, 1995-07-1995-09; Shotgun Press (Box 2, Folder 48)
        No. 5-6
        Lakewood, Ohio
      - Away / Train Wreck, Undated; Houle, David (Box 2, Folder 49)
      - Baby, I Dig You, 1994-1996; Lorimer, Sara (Box 2, Folder 50)
        No. 1-4
        Olympia, Washington; Cambridge, Massachusetts
      - Banan, 1985-07 (Box 2, Folder 51)
        Sweden
      - Be My Friend, 1981-09-1982-05; Marine, Terry (Box 7, Folder 4)
        No. 2, 4
        San Diego, California
      - Beautifully Worthless, The, 1999; Liebegott, Ali (Box 2, Folder 52)
        Part 1
        Brooklyn, New York
      - Bedwetting Tabloid, Winter; Adam; Swift (Box 12, Folder 51)
      - Behind the Zion Curtain, 1981-1989 (Box 2, Folder 53)
        Utah
      - Belly Button Comix, 2004-11; Sophie; Fantagraphics; Oog and Blik (Box 12, Folder 52)
        Amsterdam, Netherlands
      - Ben is Dead, 1990-12-1992-11; Romeo, Darby (Box 2, Folder 54)
        No. 11, 16-17
        Hollywood, California
      - Ben is Dead, 1997-1998; Romeo, Darby (Box 2, Folder 55)
        No. 27-28
      - Ben is Dead, 1998-1999; Romeo, Darby (Box 2, Folder 56)
        No. 29-30
      - Beware the Solar Flare, 1990-1999; Ed; Jam Comix (Box 2, Folder 57)
      - Big Takeover, The, 1992-02; Rabid, Jack (Box 12, Folder 53)
        No. 9
        New York, New York
      - Bike Punk Chronicles, The, 1995; Rymodee (Box 12, Folder 54)
        Pensacola, Florida
      - Bitch Magazine, Feb/Mar '94; Lara (Box 12, Folder 55)
        No. 7 (split with Lost Cause no. 2)
        Richmond, Virginia
      - Black Butterflies, 1990; Rhorn (Box 2, Folder 58)
      - Bleats n' Squonx, 1995; Criterion (Box 2, Folder 59)
      - Blowin' Chunx, 1992; Alyssa (Box 2, Folder 60)
        Ann Arbor, Michigan; Brookline, Massachusetts
      - Blues for Franklin Avenue, 1991-10; Mahto, Jamison C. (Box 2, Folder 51)
      - Bob, The, 1982-12-1983-01; Beaudoin, Gregory (Box 7, Folder 6)
        Wilmington, Delaware
      - Boo Boo, 1994; Sokol, Brett (Box 2, Folder 62)
        Cleveland, Ohio
      - Book .001, 1980; Wojciechowski, E.R. (Box 12, Folder 56)
      - Book Review, 2007-2008; Swain, Troy (Box 2, Folder 63)
      - Brain Dead, 1990-1999; Bergin, John (Box 2, Folder 64)
        Kansas City, Missouri
      - Brazen Hussy, 1998-08 (Box 12, Folder 57)
        Chattanooga, Tennessee
      - Breakfast Served All Day, 1996-02-1998-08; Gerlach, John (Box 2, Folder 65)
        No. 2, 5
      - Brooklyn!, 1995; Argoff, Fred (Box 2, Folder 66)
      - Burn Collector, 1995-2000; Burian, Al (Box 2, Folder 67)
        No. 6-7, 9, 12
        Carrboro, North Carolina
      - Burning Farm, 1992-12-1993-04; Jane (Box 2, Folder 68)
        Olympia, Washington
      - Butt Ugly, 1992; Von Bohlen, Cory (Box 2, Folder 69)
        Waukesha, Wisconsin
      - California Blackout, 1996; Lee, Ricky (Box 12, Folder 58)
      - Cats Hate Cops, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 70)